(Leonard:)Why are you reading
Pride and Prejudice?
(Sheldon:)I'll tell you why.
(Sheldon:)Amy ruined
Raiders of the Lost Ark for me,
(Sheldon:)so now I'm trying to find something
beloved to her and ruin that.
(Howard:)Because her life wasn't enough?
Wait. How can anyone ruin
Raiders? It's perfect.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, except for the fact
(Sheldon:)that Indiana Jones is completely
irrelevant to the story.
(Sheldon:)With or without him, the Nazis find
the ark, open it, and die.
(GRUMBLING)
(Howard:)Hey, wait a minute. No, the Nazis
were digging in the wrong place.
(Howard:)The only reason they got the ark
was because Indy found it first.
(Leonard:)Actually, they were only digging
in the wrong place
(Leonard:)because Indy had the medallion.
(Leonard:)Without him, they would have had
the medallion and dug in the right place.
(GRUMBLING)